<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Liopol2Blog</title>
    <link>https://liopol2blog.netlify.app/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Liopol2Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>leonardosoumas3@gmail.com (Liopol2)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>leonardosoumas3@gmail.com (Liopol2)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:40:58 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://liopol2blog.netlify.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ytdw</title>
      <link>https://liopol2blog.netlify.app/projects/ytdw/ytdw/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:40:58 -0300</pubDate><author>leonardosoumas3@gmail.com (Liopol2)</author>
      <guid>https://liopol2blog.netlify.app/projects/ytdw/ytdw/</guid>
      <description>La pirateria es mala, peeeeeeeeeeeeeero.&#xA;No enserio, jamas podria apoyar el robo de la propiedad intelectual de otra persona. Dicho esto, tampoco puedo apoyar financieramente a una empresa que roba contenido para sus trabajos propios de los cuales recibe un redito financiero, o mismamente, de empresas que exprimen miles de millones de dolares a projectos open source , aprovechando la naturaleza de los mismo, sin aportar absolutamente nada de vuelta.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flats.sh</title>
      <link>https://liopol2blog.netlify.app/projects/flats.sh/flats.sh/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 23:21:02 -0300</pubDate><author>leonardosoumas3@gmail.com (Liopol2)</author>
      <guid>https://liopol2blog.netlify.app/projects/flats.sh/flats.sh/</guid>
      <description>Nada como un nuevo inicio, ya sea un nuevo dia, nuevo trabajo, nuevo auto, o porque no nuevo sistema.&#xA;Pero desgraciadamente, siempre que empezamos de 0 hay cosas que cambiar, para dejar todo a nuestro gusto, Este es mi caso cada que decido probar una nueva distro o cuando mi sistema lleva demasiado tiempo sin un buen reset.&#xA;Durante los a単os descubri un par de cosas para hacer mi vida un poco mas facil reinstalando linux, aqui voy a compartir mis experiencias practicas y una de mis herramientas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recomended Programs</title>
      <link>https://liopol2blog.netlify.app/posts/recomendedprograms/recomendedprograms/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 19:44:39 -0300</pubDate><author>leonardosoumas3@gmail.com (Liopol2)</author>
      <guid>https://liopol2blog.netlify.app/posts/recomendedprograms/recomendedprograms/</guid>
      <description>This is a list of FREE programs that I&amp;rsquo;ve colleted over time, in no particular order that I think a common user needs to know, even if it does not fit your use case, or if you do not find a use for them at this point&#xA;General Utilities Syncthing Syncthing it&amp;rsquo;s a simple utility that you can set and forget that allows you to sync your data across multiple devices, free and open source, available in linux, windows, android and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Windows Optimization</title>
      <link>https://liopol2blog.netlify.app/posts/windowsoptimization/windowsoptimization/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 19:43:00 -0300</pubDate><author>leonardosoumas3@gmail.com (Liopol2)</author>
      <guid>https://liopol2blog.netlify.app/posts/windowsoptimization/windowsoptimization/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s face it, even though a bunch of people like to dunk on it, and with a lot of valid points, most of the population does end up using microsoft OS for most of their daily desktop computing needs, be it work or leisure, it market share it&amp;rsquo;s undeniable.&#xA;Altough there has been a huge raise of linux users with the release of the various versions of the steam deck, Windows is by far the most used desktop operative system.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Linux on a nutshell</title>
      <link>https://liopol2blog.netlify.app/posts/linux/linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jul 2024 00:02:56 -0300</pubDate><author>leonardosoumas3@gmail.com (Liopol2)</author>
      <guid>https://liopol2blog.netlify.app/posts/linux/linux/</guid>
      <description>Desktop Linux users are the vegans of technology, annoying and obnuxious individuals which have to let you know that they are moraly superior because they belong to the penguin side, but is it any truth to their claims is it any reason for a &amp;ldquo;normal&amp;rdquo; person to switch to linux?.&#xA;Today we will discuss points against and on favor of GNU/Linux Systems.&#xA;Let&amp;rsquo;s start from the bad side of linux, this is a short list of reasons for you to stay away, or do some more research on the topic before jumping head first into this OS&amp;hellip; s?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://liopol2blog.netlify.app/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2024 22:37:09 -0300</pubDate><author>leonardosoumas3@gmail.com (Liopol2)</author>
      <guid>https://liopol2blog.netlify.app/about/</guid>
      <description>Whoami I&amp;rsquo;m a person which likes to fidget with technology, eventually I got a job where I get paid to program, and fund some of my proyects (including this one), also to pay for the ever-increasingly cost of living and the deligthful server-grade hardware that I can afford.&#xA;What I want this place to be: I am open to any idea, to the point to which I&amp;rsquo;m not even sure if the entirety of this site is going to be written exclusively in one language.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Laptops Gamers</title>
      <link>https://liopol2blog.netlify.app/posts/laptops-gamer/laptops-gamer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 17:19:04 -0300</pubDate><author>leonardosoumas3@gmail.com (Liopol2)</author>
      <guid>https://liopol2blog.netlify.app/posts/laptops-gamer/laptops-gamer/</guid>
      <description>Peque単a nota antes de empezar:&#xA;Como habran notado por la fecha del post, este es un articulo que escribi hace ya un par de a単os, y que por multiples razones nunca vio la luz, pero ya que logre recuperarlo quize tambien agregarlo aca, puede que la informacion este desactualizada pero por lo que pude leer es bastante reelevante todavia.&#xA;Buenas, Si estas pensando en cambiar tu pc gamer por una laptop, no metas la pata como yo, tene en cuenta un par de cosas antes de hacer nada.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Los iconos en el escritorio</title>
      <link>https://liopol2blog.netlify.app/posts/rendimiento-de-iconos/rendimiento-de-iconos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2022 17:19:04 -0300</pubDate><author>leonardosoumas3@gmail.com (Liopol2)</author>
      <guid>https://liopol2blog.netlify.app/posts/rendimiento-de-iconos/rendimiento-de-iconos/</guid>
      <description>Wenas.&#xA;Hoy voy a hablar de lo mucho que me molesta la informacion antigua en tiempos modernos.&#xA;Resulta que un familiar me dijo hace ya un par de a単os, que si le quitas los iconos al escritorio, el sistema inicia mas rapido, consume menos ram, baja el dolar, y se acaba el hambre.&#xA;Capaz estoy exagerando un poco, pero en definitiva, que vas notar una mejora considerable por sacar unos iconos del escritorio, siendo que la primera vez que escuche esto todavia tenia una pc de un solo hilo, era entendible.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
